supremeindia.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We have accordingly developed this Privacy Policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential.We do everything we reasonably can, to protect your rights of privacy on systems and the website, controlled by us. We oftenwhy may provide hyperlinks to third party websites for product related information. We are not liable for any unauthorized or unlawful disclosures of your personal and confidential information made by those third parties, who are not subject to our control.You should take note that the information and privacy practices of such sites, may be different from ours. Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without prior notice. 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you, when you register on our site,place an order or fill out a form. The following information will be collected

  * Name and email address 
  * Contact information including phone number
  * Demographic information such as postcode
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys   

**Where do we use your information?**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons.  

  * To process the transaction  

  * Internal record keeping
  * To improve our customer service

**How do we protect your information?**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information, when you place an order or register. We do not disclose our customer information to other parties on any reason.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, we may offer third party services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. So we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.

**Limitations On Liability**

IN NO EVENT WILL SUPREME OR ITS AFFILIATES OR ANY PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DELIVERING THE SITE OR ITS PRODUCTS OR SERVICES BE LIABLE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS, USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY FAILURE OR PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE (INCLUDING LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, AND DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM INACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION OR INCONVENIENCE, DELAY, OR LOSS OF THE USE OF THE SITE). THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS APPLY WHETHER THE ALLEGED LIABILITY IS BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER BASIS, EVEN IF SUPREME OR ITS AFFILIATES OR ANY OTHER PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
